spinity.com 2017-02-21

# Spinity - Privacy policy

THIS POLICY RELATES TO THE MANNER IN WHICH THE COMPANY TREATS PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT IT COLLECTS AND RECEIVES.

THIS POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO THE PRACTICES OF MERCHANTS OR TO PEOPLE THAT THE COMPANY DOES NOT EMPLOY OR MANAGE.

BY DISCLOSING PERSONAL DATA TO THE COMPANY, THE CUSTOMER SIGNIFIES HIS CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, PROCESSING AND USE OF HIS PERSONAL INFORMATION BY THE COMPANY AS DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY.

## 1\. Definitions

  * **“Affiliated Company(ies)”** means other group companies who offer services in conjunction with the services offered by the Company.
  * **“Company”** means Spinity Limited, a limited liability company organized and registered under the laws of Malta, with its head office located at Vincenti Buildings, 28/19, Strait Street, Valletta, Malta (hereinafter "the Company");
  * **“Customer”** means any person who registers on the Website in accordance with Paragraph 3.1 hereunder;
  * **“Customer’s Account”** means a virtual account in the Customer’s name which is opened on the Website;
  * **“Personal information”** means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person;
  * **“Website”** means spinity.com

## 2\. Information Collection and Use

2.1 | 

The Company collects personal information when a Customer registers with the Website and when the Customer uses the Website in any manner. The Company may also combine information it possesses with information it obtains from other Affiliated Companies.  
  
---|---  
2.2 | 

The Company stores all the information entered during the process of a Customer’s registration on the Website. The Company also collects and stores information relating to a Customer’s transactions with the Company and third parties. The Company automatically receives and records information from the Customer’s computer and browser, including the Customer’s IP address, software and hardware attributes, and pages requested.  
  
2.3 | 

The Company uses information to personalize the Customer’s experience in order to better respond to the Customer’s individual needs, to improve the Website and the services it offers, to improve customer service, to contact the Customer when required, to process transactions and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external purposes.  
  
2.4 | 

The Company offers the option to inform the Customer about third party products and events. The Customer may opt out of these notifications in the process of signing up for a Customer Account. Where the Customer does not opt out during the signing up process, the Customer retains the opportunity to opt out of these notifications at any subsequent time by notifying the Company of his intention to unsubscribe on [webmaster@spinity.com](mailto:webmaster@spinity.com)  
  
2.5 | 

The Company will retain data while the Customer’s Account remains in operation and thereafter will be retained for a duration necessary by law.  
  
## 3\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

3.1 | 

The Company does not rent, sell, or share personal information about the Customer with non- affiliated companies but reserves the right to share such information for purposes otherwise deemed legal in accordance with the Malta Data Protection Act (Chapter 440 of the Laws of Malta).  
  
---|---  
3.2 | 

The Affiliated Companies’ websites have separate and independent privacy policies. The Company therefore has no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these websites. Nonetheless, the Company seeks to protect the integrity of the Website at all times.  
  
3.3 | 

Without prejudice to anything contained in this Privacy Policy, the Company reserves the right to disclose Personal Information relating to you to any third party if such disclosures are necessary inter alia for the following purposes:

  * for the purpose of preventing, detecting or suppressing fraud;
  * to protect and defend our rights and property or that of users of the Website;
  * to protect against abuse, misuse or unauthorised use of the Website;
  * to protect the personal safety or property of users of the Website (e.g. if you provide false or deceptive information about yourself or attempt to pose as someone else, the Company shall disclose any information it may have about the Customer in its possession so as to assist any type of investigation into the Customer’s actions);
  * for any purpose that may be necessary for the performance of any agreement the Customer may have entered into with the Company; or
  * as may be allowed or required by or under any law.

## 4\. Editing and Deleting Account Information and Preferences

4.1 | 

The Customer may access and/or edit his own account information, at any time.  
  
---|---  
4.2 | 

The Company reserves the right to send the Customer certain communications relating to the Company’s service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and other messages considered as part of the Customer Account, without offering the Customer the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.  
  
4.3 | 

The Customer can delete his Customer Account by sending an e-mail to clearly requesting such deletion to [webmaster@spinity.com](mailto:webmaster@spinity.com). In the event of deletion of an account, the Company will retain the Personal Information for as long as is necessary according to law. When the Personal Information has been kept for a period that satisfies all other legal obligations, it will be permanently destroyed.  
  
## 5\. Confidentiality and Security

5.1 | 

The Company limits access to the Customer’s Personal Information to employees who reasonably need to come into contact with such information to provide products or services to the Customer.  
  
---|---  
5.2 | 

By its very nature however the Internet is not a secure medium and data sent via this medium can potentially be subject to unauthorised acts by third parties. The Company cannot guarantee the privacy or confidentiality of any information passing over the Website. The Company shall accept no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the security of your data while in transit through the Internet.  
  
5.3 | 

In order to protect the confidentiality of the Customer’s Information, the Company makes use of SSL technology. SSL technology is designed so the information entered on the Customer’s browser is encrypted before being transmitted.  
  
## 6\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

6.1 | 

The Company may update this Privacy Policy at any time but will notify the Customer of any significant changes in the manner in which the Company treats personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in the Customer Account or by placing a notice on the Website.  
  
---|---  
6.2 | 

Any questions regarding this privacy policy should be referred to [support@spinity.com](mailto:support@spinity.com)  
  
Privacy Policy Spinity Limited

November 2012
